Yes, see, the numbers of Mama entry are very
good, so short term money has moved into that, but I am still
thinking bank
category and that I will tell you 37,000, whatever you say Bank
Nifty is going to come, whether it comes in 15 days or
a month, but there is a front in banks and there is a lot
in midcap banks, today the
commentary that has come in Bandhan Bank and Aamir Khan
Microfinance, they say that landing is
dam recovery 25%, September tweet
98% 100, I request you to get
famous in Bandhan, RBL Bank, IDFC, you will be rich report, let me
give you an update of midcap bank, Rubaru Circle, but I had
given you anti finance at 9350 earlier, it went to
95.50, book profit in that and
making ₹2 handsome, you have two picks here,
I would also like to say that for Tube Bank 1035,
I gave a target of 1150, it has become 1185, so
probably the value of Micro Finance Law and Urban
Bank category Under-21 team are today's two
picks, if you are there then I  Start the phone ji machine
safe, if you are there then the
first one will be ICICI Lombard
Insurance from the ground and Insurance Guddu
Yadav stream ICICI Lombard and
testing 1658 character 215 346 1540
take it with a stoploss of 1510 12 going back to
more than 60 Bahubali my favorite
updates UP Bank of Baroda Bank of
Baroda will give the highest record profit in this quarter
which is your July end episode
220 in eighty-four and a half take that bus stop
love 7250 this day to ₹90 ok so Bank of
Baroda ambulance packing machine safa on such a long reference
today's hot topic of
discussion na market is hot there of
your what is the reward of matches should you invest money should you invest
in the final of 7276 rupees
see this Harshita whatever is the trend, he was
telling this stands and friends let's
everyone this parking rate price to
perfection body stock will make money over next to
Years to figure out where
winds and used to give you are you written off
just it's new is a no brainer like I told you
earlier there is no metric of its valuation
so it's difficult for us to comment
but I think you should be in your portfolio in
small quantities on this very conservative
opinion machine snake
seems to be taking a red opinion right now and on midcap IT
machine there is no particular reason why you are
seeing such tremendous momentum in midcap IT
I had found my mitts so this ruling
was the rut for reminder this we have
gone from very low still I think in reality should I go
into National Tech, Tech Mahindra day will give you what you want
but next N I am by
students Lapet Yadav banking stocks we
exposed Bank of Baroda is 140 so I will pay
attention to that or RBL I
see 400 or 350 and so I am
meeting I am very bullish on the bank
and this is the only one but I like it judgment what
party has been very very big  Outperformer
however most awaited car in capturing ball
real ball swing of midcap banks so
midcap bank management Bank of Baroda and
machine sir on bell since many time you have been seeing a
pistol call and technical call as well,
next fifty minutes have passed, pay
attention to their interest, you are
seeing a lot of volume, if you are Rachna then please
present the
chart of India Bulls Housing here, they
knocked yesterday with a boom and now the volume is
seen coming with you, please
tell me on this trolley
what is your opinion on India Bulls Housing Finance, Rachna ji
was British to leave his active - politics has been
inside before but when